翻译：Luna  吃货丁小七
翻译：西兰花小贱  小英的小号
校对：cath
总监：somehacker
后期：Sung
没有鱼道
No fish ladders.
我还以为水坝必须设置鱼道
I thought they all had to have fish ladders.
不知道他们是怎么做到的
Wonder how they got around that one.
不过他们肯定有水泵
But they got to have vacuums.
把鱼直接抽出来  扔到卡车后面
Well, shoot 'em out into the back of a truck...
我想那是只黄鹂
Think that was an oriole.
我不知道这还有那种鸟
I didn't know we had those.
在这等着
Wait here.
你没好好等着
You didn't wait.
乔希去哪了
Where's Josh?
散步去了
He took a walk.
我们看到  灾难正在各地
The disaster we see is happening everywhere
同时发生
at the same time.
危机迫在眉睫
The clock is ticking.
自工业革命开始
It has been ticking for 150 years now,
至今已过去了150年
since the dawn of industrialization.
我们一味执迷于利益  产品
We are a culture hooked on profit, production,
永无止境的增长
and perpetual growth,
但代价又是什么
but at what cost?
灾难正在吞噬我们的农场
The disaster is happening to our farmlands.
我们的海洋
It is happening to our oceans,
我们的森林和野生动物
our forests, our wildlife.
它正影响着我们的气候
It is happening to our climate.
要用多久人类才能明白
How long will it be until humanity understands
万事万物都是互相联系的
that everything is interconnected?
要用多久跨国公司才能明白
How long until multinational corporations
他们不能从垂死的星球上获取利益
understand that they can't make a profit off a dead planet?
所以让我们在全球范围内开始这场革命
So let the revolution begin, all around the globe.
每位公民必须站起来投入这场战斗
An army of individual citizens must rise up and take a stand
为了未来  为了人类  为了地球
for the future, for the people,
表明立场
and for the planet.
谢谢你们
Thank you.
感谢来参加活动的所有人
Thank you all for coming out.
今晚影片制作人也来到了现场
And as you know, we have the filmmaker here tonight,
来自尤金市的洁基·克里斯蒂森
Jackie Christianson from Eugene.
这真是个绝妙的  了不起的杰作
That was tremendous, amazing work.
非常感谢你能与我们分享
Thank you so much for sharing that with us.
现在如果你们有任何问题
Now if you have any questions,
她已经准备好一一解答
she's ready to take them if you've got them.
-对吗  洁基  -是的
- Is that right, Jackie? - Yeah.
我只想感谢你  洁基
Yeah, I just want to thank you, Jackie,
分享振奋人心  带给人们希望的视频
for that uplifting, hopeful vision there.
真的很棒
It was really awesome.
我觉得如果你用
I feel like if you bombard people
这么多可怕的图片吓唬人
with too many horrific images,
只会让人觉得为时已晚  难以应对
it just feels like it's too late or too much to take on.
它充满了末日情怀
It fulfills the end-of-world vision.
指望那些人的话
Well, you're not going to get anywhere
什么也做不了
with those people anyway.
迪娜
Dena?
我想说  即便是世界末日
Yeah, I mean, end of the world,
又能损失什么
what's there really to lose?
但洁基  我很好奇  你认为
But, Jackie, I'm curious... What you think it is exactly
我们究竟要怎么做
that we're supposed to do?
你有什么伟大的计划吗
Do you have some sort of big plan or?
我想  这种指望一个伟大的计划的想法
I think this one big plan thinking
导致了很多我们正在面临的问题
leads to a lot of the problems we're facing.
对于我来说  不应该认为
Part of the idea for me, is not thinking
只有一个伟大的计划
there's just one big thing.
我不想专注于什么伟大的计划
I'm not focused on big plans.
我只想专注于小计划
I'm focused on small plans.
很多小计划
A lot of small plans.
我想只要我们齐心协力
I think just by us coming together
共同关心一件事
and sharing our concerns in one...
我们什么时候跟你的人见面
What time are we meeting your guy?
我们约好11点
We said 11:00.
11点
11:00.
我们肯定到不了
We're not gonna make it.
那家伙看起来也没什么事要做
The guy didn't really seem like he had a lot going on.
我可以给他打个电话
I could give him a call, though.
不  不
No, no.
我现在不想去找公共电话
I don't want to find a pay phone right now.
放轻松  乔希
Breathe, Josh.
好吧
Okay.
我们很快就能到
We'll be there soon.
一切都好
All is well.
舷内配有5L的V8发动机
Got a inboard 5-liter V-8 engine.
它看起来真的很漂亮
Well, it looks really nice.
是啊  这是艘很棒的船
Yeah. It's a great boat.
-有点舍不得她  -那是肯定的
- Kind of hate to get rid of her. - I'm sure.
我可以告诉你  开船去滑水很开心
Lot of good skiing, I can tell you that.
但是  该做出改变了
But, you know, time for a change.
两个孩子都去了大学
Both kids off to college.
不过开船去滑水还是很开心
Lot of good skiing though.
请问能用下您的卫生间吗
May I use your bathroom?
当然
Uh, yeah, sure.
穿过那边车库上楼
Through the garage there, up the stairs.
-谢谢  -没事
- Thanks. - Yeah.
我是护士  他在超市工作
I'm a nurse. He works at a supermarket.
哪一个
What one?
你们应该修理一下那些刹车灯
You definitely want those brake lights working.
好了  准备就绪
All right, we're good.
好啊
All right.
我们一直想要一艘船
Well, we've always wanted a boat.
真不敢相信美梦成真  对吗  亲爱的
Can't believe this is happening, right, honey?
不  我不饿
No, not hungry.
我们快到了吗
Are we almost there?
我们现在一定是在怀俄明州
We must be in Wyoming by now,
下一站是达科塔州
coming up on the Dakotas.
我不知道  也许还要半小时
I don't know. Half an hour, maybe.
他住得挺远
He's pretty out there.
你之前说他住得很近
I thought you said he lived close.
是的
He does.
很近
This is close.
这才是很近
我们已经走了这么远
We've already gone like this.
现在要走这么远吗
Are we going like this?
如果是的话就直说
You can tell me, if we are.
离现在的位置很近  好吧
It's close for here, okay?
又不是康尼狄格州
This isn't Connecticut.
-不是吗  -不是
- It's not? - No.
糟糕  我肯定是下错站了
Shit, I must've got off on the wrong train.
那是什么
What is that?
鹿
Deer.
你要停车
You're stopping?
它身子在路上
It's half in the road.
还有体温
It's warm.
什么意思
What does that mean?
是只母鹿
It's a doe.
她怀孕了
She's pregnant.
宝宝还活着
The baby's alive in there.
天啊
Oh, my God.
你们从哪弄来的
Where'd you get this thing?
梅德福市
Medford.
-派对游艇  -是的
- Party barge. - Yeah.
你肯定是迪
You must be D.
你是臭名昭著的哈
You're the infamous H.
很高兴见到你
Nice to meet you.
乐意为您效劳
At your service.
夜色行动
Night Moves?
聪明
Slick.
其实可以叫  去钓鱼或者春梦
We could've had Gone Fishin' or Wet Dream,
可那听上去有点逊
but those sounded kind of lame.
还可以叫  兴风作浪  迷乱荒野
There was Makin' Waves, Reel Wild.
理解吗  和鱼线轴是一个词
Get it? Reel, two Es.
挺不错吧
Pretty awesome.
疯狂牙买加  乱世佳人
Jamaican Me Crazy, Gone With the Wind,
直译  随风而去
都想过了
looked at all those.
好了  你怎么想的
All right. So what do you think?
大小足够吗
Size-wise, is this gonna work?
你有钥匙吗
You got a key?
有
Yeah.
很好  空间很大
Good. Good space.
我们要把这些都拆出来
We'll take all of this out.
很好
Yeah.
你们花多少钱买的
How much this set you back anyway?
不便宜
It wasn't cheap.
肯定的
I bet.
你们用的现金  对吗
You paid cash, right?
没有  我把信用卡账号给了那个家伙
No, I gave the guy my credit card number
然后要他去查看我的网页
and then told him to check out my webpage,
然后我转发到了脸谱网上
and then I posted it on Facebook
这样所有人都能看到
so everyone else could see it too.
现金
Cash,
穷人的钱
the poor people's money.
看起来还不错
So it looks all right?
挺好的
Oh, yeah.
足够了
She'll do.
真遗憾
It's a shame.
怎么不是艘破船
It's not a bad ship here.
如果好好开  还能用好几年
It's got years left in her if you treated her right.
如果要留下
If I was keeping her,
只有几个地方要简单修理下
I'd say there are some easy repairs to do.
但我猜我们也没指望她经久耐用  对吧
But, uh, I guess we don't give a shit about longevity, do we?
确实
Nope.
见到你很高兴  哥们
Good to see you, brother.
我也是  哈蒙  好久不见
Yeah, you, too, Harmon. It's been a while.
你从来不过来找我
Well, you never come around.
你也是啊
Well, neither do you.
好吧
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
你把车停那边  好吗
Why don't you just park your rig over there, okay?
好
Yeah.
还有要把车头冲里  好吗
And then let's head back inside, all right?
因为这里经常有缉毒警察
'Cause there's narcs everywhere out here,
而且浣熊也是信不过的
and don't trust the raccoons at all!
刚印出来
Hot off the presses.
凯瑞·泰勒
Cary Taylor.
我看起来胖了点  但是无所谓了
Looks like I've gained a few pounds, but, whatever.
凯瑞·泰勒  真的吗
Cary Taylor. Really?
凯瑞·泰勒
Cary Taylor.
白痴
Fucking idiot.
明天我们就叫这个名字
Tomorrow this is who we are, all right?
没有例外
No exceptions.
约瑟夫·玛卡  1981年10月30日
Joseph Macca, 10-30-81.
你看下
Here.
我叫你乔伊吧
I'll call you Joey.
我一直觉得你应该叫乔伊
You always looked like a Joey to me.
这些看着真不错  伙计
These look really good, man.
干得好
Nice work.
我叫爱德华  就跟你们说下
I'm Edward, just so you know.
你们可以叫我爱德
You can just call me Ed.
爱德
Ed.
两人皆为著名电视主持人
爱德·麦克马洪  爱德·沙利文
Ed McMahon, Ed Sullivan.
美国政治家  反共人士
麦卡锡主义来源
乔·麦卡锡
Joe... McCarthy.
你们在路上看到新的高尔夫球场了吗
You see the new golf course on the way in?
那个是在盖高尔夫场吗
Is that what that was?
没有  我们只看到一些翻斗卡车
No, we just saw dump trucks.
是啊
Yep.
只是波特兰帝国的最新前哨所
Just the latest outpost of the Portland empire.
动物标本
And taxidermy,
奢侈美食
gourmet food,
八美元的咖啡
$8 coffee...
听起来不错
Sounds pretty cool.
操  不错
Yeah, fuck cool.
快把你们的不错收起来吧
Keep your fucking cool to yourself.
你知道本德已经有多少个高尔夫球场了吗
You know how many golf courses there are in Bend already?
-不知道  -猜猜看
- No. - Guess.
我不知道
I don't know.
猜猜
Guess.
五个
5.
15个
15.
29个
29.
这里是高原沙漠
It's the high plains desert.
去哪找水
Where's the water?
对吧
Right?
简直就是扯淡
Absolute bullshit.
好吧
Okay.
那么其他的事情进展得怎么样了
So how's everything else going?
都安排好了吗
Are we on schedule?
是的  快了
Yeah, real close.
快了  快了是什么意思
Close? What do you mean close?
我们可能还需要几百公斤的化肥
We could use another couple hundred pounds of fertilizer.
不好意思  我以为你已经都准备好了
Sorry, I thought you said that you had it all under control.
没你想的那么简单
I mean, it's not that easy.
我不能总去那里
I can't go in that often.
我还有工作
And I have to work.
好吗
Right?
那些草又不会又不会自己割掉
Those greens don't mow themselves, you know?
那你现在弄到多少
So how much-- how much do you have?
差不多450公斤
1,000 pounds, give or take.
那我们还需要多少
And how much do we need?
220公斤就可以了
500 pounds would be nice.
220公斤
500 pounds?
听着  我们可以只用现有的这些
Look, we can go with what we have.
我是说
I mean...
应该没有问题
it's probably all right.
也许那个大坝自己想倒
God knows that dam wants to come down.
那里的水那么多那么重
There is a serious tonnage of water
一直冲击着它
just pushing up against her walls.
万事万物都在让她投降放弃
Everything in the world is telling her to give up and let go.
但是  我是说
But still, I mean,
我们应该尽所能帮助她  对吗
we should just help her all we can. Right?
那你说我们该怎么做
So what-- what are you saying that we do?
早上我们先去农用品店  仅此而已
Let's go to the feed store in the morning, that's all.
他们不会卖给我们那么多
They're not gonna sell us that much.
只有一种方法能知道
There's just one way to find out.
不  只要超过五公斤
No, anything over 10 pounds
对他们来说就是危险信号
sends up major red flags for these guys.
-那不一定是真的  -是真的
- That's not necessarily true. - It is true.
我们应该尽早知道这些
We should've known about this earlier.
是啊  等一下  让我
Yeah, one second, let me just...
好吧  如果这是我们必须做的
Okay, no, if that's what we got to do.
是啊
Yeah.
好了  我们明天一早出发
All right, we'll go out in the morning.
然后回来这里给火鸡填馅
Then we'll come back here and stuff the turkey.
好吗
'Kay?
周日过去
We'll put in Sunday.
周日晚上开始行动
We'll move into position Sunday night.
周一早上
Monday morning,
我们就像什么也没发生过那样照常上班
we'll all go to work like nothing happened, okay?
他知道他在说什么吧
He knows what he's talking about?
当然
Yeah.
他接受过最好的训练
Yeah, he was trained by the best,
美国海军陆战队
the United States Marine Corps.
你信任他吗
You trust him?
当然
Definitely.
好吧  我去睡觉了
All right. I'm going to bed.
她没事吧
You think she's all right?
没事
Yeah.
她挺厉害的
Yeah, she's done some shit.
她是很棒
She's good.
在尤金市  你和她一起做的
She did that thing in Eugene with you,
手机信号塔
the cell towers?
是啊
Yeah. Yeah.
她提供的资金  我听别人说的
She bankrolled that. That's what I heard.
什么意思  你从哪听来的
What do you mean, that's what you heard?
是你告诉我的  蠢货
Well, you told me that, you dumb-ass.
很好  你是个偏执狂
That's good. You're paranoid.
长远来看  说不定这样更健康
Healthier that way in the long run.
船也是她出的钱
She paid for it.
那船要多少钱
How much was that boat?
一万美金
10 grand.
白富美
Rich daddy.
不过我不懂她为什么一定要来
I don't see why she has to be here, though.
她已经做了很多了
She's done plenty already.
这是约定的一部分
It's part of the deal.
我不懂她为什么不回家
I don't see why she just doesn't go home.
我们明早可以带她去火车站
We can take her down to the train station tomorrow morning.
这跟其他事都不一样  我的朋友
This isn't the same as those other shows, my friend.
这是在另一个高度
This is on a different level.
你知道的
You know that.
你以为我不知道吗
You think I don't know that?
-不  你知道  -好吧
- No, you know. - Okay.
你当然知道
You definitely know.
这件事会闹得很大
This is gonna be big.
肯定得闹大
Yeah, it's got to be big.
至少要能让人们开始思考
If people are going to start thinking anyway...
就为了每分每秒都能听iPod
killing all the salmon just so you can run
他们可以杀掉所有的三文鱼
your fucking iPod every second of your life.
那将成为现实
And that's what's gonna happen.
人们得开始思考
People are gonna start thinking.
他们必须开始思考
They have to.
你后来还见过兰迪吗
You ever see Randy anymore?
没有  很久没见了
No, not for a while.
上一次听说  他似乎躲在鹰溪
He was squatting in Eagle Creek, last I heard.
溜回山野里去了
Slipping back out into the wild.
幸运儿
Lucky man.
我以为这儿开门更早
I thought it opened earlier.
不好意思
I'm sorry.
不会再等太久的
It won't take that much longer.
-别担心  -我没在担心
- Don't worry. - I'm not worried.
-好吧  -不  我们得吃东西
- All right. - No, we got to eat.
顺便给迪娜一个机会做作业
It gives Dena a chance to do her homework.
我已经记住了
I've got it.
你的鸡蛋怎么样
How are your eggs?
看起来很干
They look dry.
我喜欢这种做法
I like them this way.
你应该尝尝看
You should have some.
不
No.
我早上只吃燕麦粥
I only eat oatmeal in the morning.
小女孩  你需要蛋白质
Girl, you need protein.
这样脑子才会更好使
It makes your brain fire better.
相信我  你得吃点鸡蛋
Believe me. You should have some eggs.
我的脑子已经很好使了  燕麦最棒了
My brain fires just fine, mister. Oats are the best.
-最完美的食物  -好了好了
- They're a perfect food. - Okay, okay.
他要是问你为什么要化肥  你怎么说
So what are you gonna say if he asks why you want it?
为了西兰花
For the broccoli.
为了所有需要氮素的该死的西兰花
For all the goddamn broccoli that needs its nitrogen.
我可以的
I'm fine.
别担心
Don't worry about it.
我没在担心
I'm not worried about it.
哈蒙
Harmon.
哥们儿  最近如何
Hey, man. How you doing?
没惹什么麻烦
Keeping my nose clean, you know.
那就好
Glad to hear it.
日安  兄弟
Well, you have a good day, brother.
-你也是  -放轻松
- You too. - Take it easy.
-好  -回头见
- Yep. - See you around.
这他妈怎么回事
The hell was that?
你不是说了这里没有熟人吗
I thought you said you don't know anybody around here?
我跟他不怎么熟
I barely know him.
什么叫不怎么熟
How do you barely know him?
我们一起坐过牢
We served time together.
什么
What?
你不是说自己没有前科吗
I thought you said you didn't have any priors.
这他妈什么情况
What the hell is your deal?
你本来打算什么时候告诉我们
When were you gonna tell us that?
冷静
Calm down.
很久以前的事儿  都不能算了
It's so long ago, it doesn't really count.
已经完结了  都被销案了
It's gone, expunged.
你朋友可真是个人物
Your friend is really something here,
艾德先生  或者说哈蒙
Mr. Ed-- or is it Harmon?
事情本来就已经有点复杂了
Things are kind of getting mixed up already,
我们只剩不到一个小时
and we're, what, an hour in?
你以为你的记录销了吗
You think your record is gone?
你以为记录真的会消失吗
You think anything is ever gone anymore?
跟上时代吧  老兄
You need to join this century, dude,
要知道你的案底并不只是
and realize that your record is not just sitting
被堆在某个档案柜里
in some filing cabinet somewhere.
他们不会销毁的  一切都会记录在案
They don't just burn it. Nothing is ever gone anymore.
你得认清这点
You need to know that.
放轻松点  这不是什么大事儿
Just take it easy, because it's not that big a deal.
这是一件大事
It is a big deal.
我觉得我们都得认清状况
I think we all should know what we're dealing with here.
能请你闭嘴吗
Oh, could you please shut up?
-好吧  -好的
- Okay. - Okay.
好了
All right.
记住  尽可能不要引人注意
Now remember, just be as forgettable as possible, all right?
摄像头在商店边儿上
The cameras are on the edges of the store,
所以尽量待在中间的货架那里
so stay to the middle aisle as much as possible.
别把帽子摘掉  好吗
Keep your hat on, okay?
记住  四万平方米  好吗
Hey, hey, remember, ten acres, okay?
你有四万平方米的土地
You got ten acres of land.
我在找大包装的那种
Hey, I'm looking for your larger bags?
22公斤袋装的
Your 50-pound bags?
那些在外面
Oh, they're outside,
从那个门出去的棚子里
out that door and over in the shed.
谢谢
Cool, thanks.
她还在马尼拉的时候
When she was in-- in Manila,
跟十个姐妹住同一间屋子
she shared a room with ten sisters,
过来以后
and she gets here.
她打量着房子
She looks at the house,
竟然说  这房子太小了
and she says, "The house is too small."
好了  再见  古斯
All right, hasta luego, all right, Goose?
好  日安
All right. Have a good day.
有什么能帮你的吗
Can I help you?
是的
Yeah.
我在找硝酸铵化肥
I'm looking for ammonium nitrate fertilizer.
你们有吗
Do you have that?
你都找过了吗
Did you look around?
稍微看了看
A little.
是吗
Yeah?
不  我们这儿没有
Nope, we don't have it.
一点都没有吗
None at all?
你可以去问问前台
Well, you can-- you can ask in the front office.
前台在哪里
Where's that?
在那个活动房屋里
In the trailer.
谢谢
Thanks.
有什么能帮你的吗
Can I help you?
是的
Yeah, I think so.
我想买点化肥
Looking to get some fertilizer.
有指定种类吗
Sure, you know what you're looking for?
是的  硝酸铵
Yeah, the ammonium nitrate.
希望你们这里有
Hope you've got it.
你要多少
How much you need?
220公斤
500 pounds.
如果你不介意的话
What are you growing with that,
能问一下要用来种什么吗
if you don't mind my asking?
甜菜  胡萝卜  洋葱
Oh, beets, carrots, onions,
欧洲萝卜  西兰花
parsnips, broccoli.
你用过我们的钠肥吗
I wonder if you've tried our new sodium fertilizer?
报告显示效果良好
It's good stuff by all reports,
吸收很快  跟铵肥效果一样
fast uptake, just like ammonium.
我觉得还是买我们用习惯了的吧
Yeah, I think I'll probably stick with what we're used to.
-不过谢谢你  -好吧
- Thank you, though. - All right.
你刚刚说要多少来着
How much you say you need?
220公斤
500 pounds.
土地面积多大呢
And how many acres you covering?
四万平方米
Ten.
好了
All right.
我需要你的签名和身份证
I need your signature, your ID...
拿出来了
Coming up.
没问题
Yep, no problem.
还有你的社保卡
And your Social Security card.
我没带
I don't think I have that.
我一般不带那个出门
I don't usually carry that around with me.
在卖硝酸铵给你之前
Well, I'm gonna-- I'm gonna need to see
我必须得看看
your Social Security card
你的社保卡  知道吗
before I sell you ammonium nitrate, you understand?
我能告诉你号码  这不是问题
I could tell you the number, no problem.
不  我必须得亲眼看到
No, I'm gonna need to see it--
这是受管制物品
controlled substance and all.
那好吧
Okay. All right.
让我去卡车里找一下
Well, let me-- let me go check in my truck.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
什么情况
What's up?
他要看社保卡
He wants a Social Security card.
什么
What?
胡扯
Bullshit.
完全就是胡扯  根本是故意刁难你
Complete and utter bullshit. Just a power trip.
他完全是骗你
He's making shit up.
谁会拿着社保卡满街跑
Who carries around their Social Security card?
我是这么说的  不过我说先在车上看看
That's what I said, but I told him I'd check in the car.
我们走吧  换个地方
All right, let's just go. Come on. We'll find it someplace else.
不不不
No, no, no, no.
-你是说换个地方吗  -对
- Just split you mean? - Yeah.
怎么  你不同意
What, you don't think so?
我觉得这是最容易
I'm just thinking that's the easiest way
被这里的人记住的方法
to get remembered out here, right?
我觉得你可能得回去
You probably ought to go back in there, I'd say.
不不不
No, no, no, no.
回去  告诉他你的卡放在家里了
Just go back in, tell him you left your card at home.
看看他怎么说
See what happens.
最坏的情况就是他不卖
Worst case is, he doesn't make the sale,
可你不能就这么不管他了
but you can't just leave him hanging, right?
去吧
Go on.
我没带社保卡
Yeah, I don't have that with me.
我一般不会随身带着
I don't carry that around on me usually.
这就不大方便了
Well, that's inconvenient.
对啊
Yeah, it is.
我甚至都不知道自己放哪儿了
I don't even really know where it is,
可是我需要买化肥
but I really do need that load.
有什么别的办法没有
So I don't know if there's something we can work out,
能不能跳过这一步
or some way to get around this.
你可以回家
Well, you could go home,
仔细找一下再回来  我们开到五点
take a look, come back later. We're open till 5:00.
是吗
Yeah.
我们住在松树洞那边
We're up near Pine Hollow,
得等到下周才能来了
so I wouldn't be able to get back for another week.
我也想帮你
Well, I wish I could help.
没有卡的话我今天最多能买多少
Well, how much can I get today without the card?
买不了
None.
我不能留点什么作抵押吗
I can't leave you some collateral or something?
不好意思
I'm afraid not.
先生  今年的冬天特别长
Look, sir, the winter went extra long this year,
所以我们现在施肥已经很晚了
so we're already late getting that stuff on the ground,
西兰花非常需要上肥
and the broccoli really needs it now,
不然没办法按时收获
or it's not gonna be ready in time.
我真的很抱歉
Well, I'm real sorry.
饲料对我们来说也很重要
The forage production is a big deal for us too.
我们有120头牛  需要草料和苜蓿
We've got a 120 milk cows that need that grass and clover.
只要你能带上我们要求的身份证明回来
Look, you come back here with the proper identification.
我们就能卖给你
I'm sure we can work something out.
可在那之前  我没法帮你
But until then, I can't help you.
不好意思  这是规定
I'm sorry. That's just how it is.
如果我长得像这些人你就会卖给我了吗
You'd sell it to me if I looked like these guys.
我认识这些人
I know these guys.
幸好你长得不像我们
Lucky you don't look like us.
好吧  先生
All right, look, sir.
如果你想  你可以打给我叔叔
If you want to, you can call my uncle.
我们的名字是丰收自然
Nature's Harvest is our name.
我们种植胡萝卜  洋葱  甜菜
We grow carrots, onions, beets,
欧洲萝卜  西兰花
parsnips, broccoli,
我们还有120头牛为威尔伯乳业供货
and we have 120 milk cows that supply for Wilber Dairy.
你们说不定喝过我们产的奶
You probably drink our milk.
我确实喝这个牌子
I do drink the milk
如果打折的话
if it's on sale.
你能到那边抓着绳子吗
You want to go around and grab this?
当然
Sure.
-你可以吗  -可以
- Got that? - Yeah.
所以
So...
我觉得我们应该从上游下水
I'm thinking we'll put in upstream all ways.
最近的地方是林间湖
Closest place is Lake of the Woods,
这个时节不会有什么人
not too many spectators this time of year.
好  在上游多远
Yep. How far upstream?
船坞离水库大概有
Uh, the boat launch is six or seven clicks
六七公里
from the reservoir.
我们先把船放下
We'll put the boat down first,
然后把卡车开下山
then take the truck further down the mountain.
好  听起来不错
All right, that sounds good.
你能弄好这些吗
You good with this?
可以  没问题
Yeah. I'm good.
慢点
Easy.
东西很重
Heavy load.
跟我走就行
You want to just follow me?
等等  你不是说没人会来吗
Wait, I thought you said no one would be here?
这不算什么
This is nothing.
你见识过旺季就知道了
You should see it in the on-season.
好吧
All right.
来吧  跟我来
Come on. Follow me.
好
All right.
你差一点就猜准了
You're almost right dead in the middle,
只比价格范围的正中低一点点
just a little below the very center of the price range.
来看看你能否能赢得五天六晚迈阿密之旅
Let's see if you are on your way to Miami for six nights.
她猜对了吗
Is she right?
你猜对了
You got it!
你能去迈阿密了  你能去迈阿密了
You're going to Miami! You're going to Miami!
我已经走了差不多18公里了
I've been walking for, like, 11 miles.
我走不动了
I can't go any more.
我的脚脖子要断了
My ankles are breaking.
我们很快
We'll be fast.
先找个安全的地方停拖车
Let's find a safe place to park the trailer, all right?
找停车地方的时候小心点
And careful where you park.
停车场有监控的
The lot has cameras now, okay?
知道了
Got it.
我们现在要做什么
Now what should we do?
那是个大家伙
That's a big guy.
我要射它吗
Should I shoot that?
砰
Bam!
他的胳膊断了
That guy has a broken arm.
那个家伙有胳膊
That guy has arms.
我们射它的胳膊
Let's shoot his arms!
砰  砰
Boom, Boom.
你要走哪条路回去
Which way are you going back?
26号公路  沿着山走
Uh, 26, across the mountain.
有点绕路  但是车流更多
It's out of the way, but there's more traffic.
我们可以藏进去
We can blend in.
我们分开以后最好不要再打电话
When we split up, we shouldn't talk on the phone.
对  不可以
Yeah, no way.
对  不联络  禁止联络
Yeah, no contact. No contact.
-不联络  -没错
- No contact. - Yeah.
-你们好  -靠
- Howdy. - Oh, shit.
你们今天怎么样
How are you guys doing today?
还不错
Not bad.
天气真好
Beautiful day.
不用管我  我只是出来走走
Don't mind me. I'm just out walking around.
必须一直走来走去才行
Got to keep walking all the time.
我的腿疼死了
My legs are killing me.
神经全部搭错线了
Nerves are messed up.
说起来裹脚布那么长
You don't want to hear about it.
不过  你们真会找好地方
Anyway, awesome spot you found.
对啊
Yep.
这里被重建得很好
Yeah, they fixed it up real nice.
80年代时我常到这里来
Oh, yeah, I used to come here back in the '80s.
80年代
Back in the '80s--
那是个疯狂的年代
man, those were wild times...
疯狂的年代
wild times.
保重
Take care.
这个湖有多深
How deep is this lake anyway?
这个季节大概有60米
Uh, 200 feet this time of year.
湖里有什么鱼
What kind of fish are in it?
主要是切喉鱒
Cutthroat trout, mainly.
我就见过这一种
It's all I've ever seen.
这是种油性鱼
That's an oily fish.
鳟鱼含有优质欧米茄三脂肪酸
Good omega-3 fatty acids in trout,
有益心脏
good for the heart.
据说还能抗抑郁
Good for depression too, they say.
我只知道钓这种鱼很好玩
All I know is, they're fun to catch.
怎么个好玩法
What makes them fun?
它们喜欢反抗  跳跃
They like to fight, they like to jump.
有时候能成功挣脱
Sometimes they break free,
是种令人敬佩的鱼
and I respect that in a fish.
我从来没钓过鱼
I've never fished.
不是吧  一次也没有
No, never? Not once?
-没有  -一 次 也 没 有
- Nope. - Not one time?
没有
Nope.
我小时候看过很多鱼的油画
Saw a lot of paintings of fish when I was a kid.
那是我们的家庭假期
Those were our family vacations,
通过欣赏画作来逃避现实
just looking at paintings of places we'd rather be.
总有一天你会去钓鱼的
Someday you'll fish.
不会的
No.
我现在不想钓鱼
I'm not fishing now.
2048年  海洋生物将完全灭绝
In 2048, the oceans are gonna be empty.
是吗  谁说的
Yeah? Who says?
科学
Science.
科学  也许科学错了
Science? Maybe science is wrong.
不会的
No.
29%的可食用鱼类数量下降了九成
29% of edible fish have gone down by 90%.
沿海人口的上涨
More people are moving to the coastlines,
意味着更多污染与垃圾
means more pollution, more waste.
情况会成几何级数地恶化
Situation is getting "geometically" worse.
最后一切都结束得很快
It'll all go fast in the end.
海洋丧失生物多样性后  一切随之消逝
Once the marine biodiversity goes, everything goes with it.
你知道得挺多
You know a lot.
大学时听过的唯一一门好课
The one good class I took in college.
是吗  没别的了吗
Really? That's it?
那真是太遗憾了
I hate to hear that.
我大学没读多久
I wasn't there very long.
四年培养出一群装逼佬
Just a bunch of poseurs shooting up for four years
毕业后到纽约从事媒体工作
before they took their media jobs in New York.
简直是个笑话  我迫不及待想离开那里
It was a joke. I couldn't wait to get out of there.
你应该趁一切消逝前去钓鱼
You should go fishing some time before it's all gone.
那个位置不妙啊
That's not a good spot.
确实
No.
我的车爆胎了
Yeah, I got a flat.
我想我需要你帮忙
Yeah, well you know, I'm gonna need your help.
是  是  我有
Yeah, yeah, I got--
不  我有  对  这个
no, I got-- yeah, this--
就在这里
yeah, it's right here.
对  我确实有千斤顶
Yes, I do have a jack.
宝贝  真希望你能看到
Babe, I wish you could see this.
我现在是多么威武雄壮
I'm looking pretty manly right now.
车已经被抬起来了
Okay, car is in the air.
我需要抬多高
How far am I going with this?
-你可以暂停倒计时吗  -好吧
- Can you stop it? - Okay.
不是个好主意
Not a great idea.
我们可以走了
Hey, we're good.
靠
Shit.
好  很好
Okay. Okay.
再会  兄弟
Later, brother.
再见  迪
See you, D!
好的
Okay.
现在我们只需要回家
We just got to get home,
明天一早去工作
show up for work tomorrow morning,
一切照常  好吗
just get back to normal, okay?
你在听我说吗
Hey, are you listening to me?
在啊
Uh, yeah.
很好
Okay.
靠
Shit.
把安全带系上
Put your seat belt on.
晚上好  我是塔兰特警察局的
Good evening, I'm Sergeant Snook
斯努克警官
with the Talent Police Department.
我们现在在检查这片区域
We're just checking the area right now,
清查来往人员的证件
identifying everybody coming through.
我需要看一下你的驾照
I need to see your license.
没问题
Yeah, of course.
你们今晚过得怎么样
How are you guys doing tonight?
我们挺好的
Oh, we're doing good.
好  你的乘客呢
Good. How about your passenger?
我也需要看你的证件
I need to see some ID for you.
约瑟夫·玛卡
俄勒冈州尤金市
茵维尔街25号
约瑟夫  麻烦你下车  可以吗
Joseph, would you mind stepping out of the vehicle for me?
我想在这里问你一些问题
I'd just like to talk to you over here.
好
Yeah.
麻烦你掀开这块防水布好吗
Why don't you lift up this tarp here?
我需要检查它底下放了什么
I need to see what's underneath there.
你能掀开它吗
Can you lift that up for me?
好
Yeah.
那个箱子呢
How about the box?
可以把箱子滑过来吗
Could you slide the box over here?
你能让我看看箱子里面吗
Do you mind if I take a look inside?
你介意我看一下箱子内容吗
Do you mind if I look inside?
不介意
No.
这是个社区农业箱
That's just, like-- a CSA box.
农产品直销本地社区
It's, like, community supported agriculture
送货上门  全是蔬菜
for home delivery, just vegetables.
好  约瑟夫
Okay, Joseph.
你有没有发现任何形迹可疑的
You didn't see anything coming through, did you,
反常的事情呢
that looked out of the ordinary to you?
-没有  -没有  好
- No. - No, okay.
这是你们的证件
Here's your guys' IDs back.
-谢谢  祝你晚上过得愉快  -好
- Thanks, and have a good night. - Okay.
晚安
Good evening.
你好
Hi.
我是塔兰特警察局的斯努克警官
I'm Sergeant Snook with the Talent Police Department.
就你那组织能力根本不能
You wouldn't have the organization skills
策划完成这样的行动
to pull off something like that.
你的审问能力也不怎么样
You don't have good interrogation skills.
很明显  这些人还是有点组织能力的
Well, clearly, these people have some organizational skills.
-早上好  -早
- Good morning. - Hey.
我以为你还没回来呢
I didn't know you were back already.
我夜里到的
Oh, yeah, yeah. I got in late.
那份上面没有当地新闻
Nothing local on there, you know.
如果你想知道比佛利山庄的人都在干什么
Unless you want to see what's happening in Beverly Hills
那还能看看
every five seconds of the day, then cool.
如果要知道家门口的河里发生了什么
But if you want to see what's happening
对不起  没有
in your own river, sorry.
怎么了
What's going on?
昨天晚上有人炸了格林彼得大坝
Somebody blew up the Green Peter Dam last night.
大事件  全国性新闻
Big story, national news.
有个人在下游
And this guy was downriver,
睡在河岸边
sleeping on the bank.
现在失踪了
Now they can't find him.
我再也不要去露营了
I am never going camping again,
除非是去山上
well, unless I'm uphill.
天  这家伙真倒霉
God, what a bummer.
你能想象吗
Can you imagine that?
就像是"兄弟  不要打鼾了"
It's like, "Dude, quit snoring."
"等等"
"Wait a minute."
"一大波湖水正在靠近"
"There's an entire lake coming for us."
-"我靠"  -一点都不好笑  迪伦
- "Holy shit!" - That's so funny, Dylan.
你真是毫无同情心
You have, like, no feelings at all.
不好意思呢
Oh, I'm sorry that my sympathy's
我支持炸掉大坝
with the water on this one.
好吧  你真是疯了
Wow, okay. Now you're insane.
不是啊  拜托
No, come on.
当然  如果那家伙真出事了
Like, of course, if something happened to that guy,
那真是太惨了
that's awful.
我希望他们能找到他  真的
I hope they find him. I do.
我只是想说
I'm just saying...
总要有人先开始做点什么
someone's got to start somewhere, you know?
真的
Seriously.
怎么  肖恩  你不同意
What, Sean, you don't agree?
确实  他们是群白痴  仅此而已
No, they're idiots, that's all.
对  但你不觉得他们挺有道理的吗
Yeah, but you don't think they had a point?
是啊  他们当然有很好的理由
Yeah, sure, they had a fine point.
但一座大坝  谁会在意呢
But one dam? Who cares?
那条河上建了十座大坝
That river has ten dams on it.
到处都有供电网
The grid is everywhere.
至少需要炸掉差不多12座
You need to take down, like,
100座大坝才会有影响
12 dams to make a difference, 100.
一座根本不算什么
Doesn't do anything.
怎么  你想要一座核电站
And, what, you want a nuke plant?
因为说到底这是唯一一个其他的选择
Because that's your only other option when you get down to it.
不  我是说希望每个人都能节约点
No, no. I'm just saying I want everyone to use less.
难道这样很难做到吗  至少这是件大事
I mean, is that so much to ask? I mean, it's something, you know?
没错  这确实是一项宣言
Yeah, it's a statement, right.
但我对宣言不感兴趣  我要的是结果
I'm not interested in statements. I'm interested in results.
拜托  你觉得这不是一种结果吗
Seriously, you don't call that results?
不  这叫吸引眼球
No, I call that theater.
好吧  那你有什么解决方法
All right, well, what's your solution?
看看窗外
Look out the window.
这样很慢  但我觉得有意义多了
It's a lot slower, but it makes a lot more sense to me.
你玩得开心吗
You have a good time?
那是波特兰
It was Portland.
看上去你玩得很开心
It looks like you had a good time.
我只是有点累
I'm just-- I'm tired.
你住在哪里
Where'd you stay?
我住朋友家  他刚搬到市里
I stayed at this friend's house. The guy just moved to town.
快点  你们两个  今天有大规模生产
Come on, you two, we start mass today.
不
Oh, no!
差点没了
Almost lost it.
好啦
There we go.
很好
Okay, that's good.
我感觉到什么了
I feel something.
看看
Look at that!
妈妈  看我的灵气
Mom, look at my aura!
很美
Beautiful. Okay.
我也要试试看
I want to try that!
好的  等我一下
Okay, give me a second.
这说明他有精神力量
Yeah, that means he's spiritual.
菲利斯
Hey, Felix!
不  你的灵气下降了
No, your aura level just went down.
放手  放手
Let go, let go.
乔希
Hey, Josh.
你想让我测你的灵气颜色吗
You want me to read your aura?
真的有用
It works.
好吧
Okay.
-你看过这个吗  -嗨  柯尔瑟
- Have you seen this thing? - Hey, Corser.
-这是什么  -我的灵气测试仪
- What is it? - It's my aura reader.
我测过  纯黑色
Oh, I've seen it. It's all black.
-好吧  -不好意思
- Yeah, okay. - Sorry.
是时候看看你们的真面目了
Now it's time to see who you people really are.
乔希
Hey, Josh.
柯尔瑟
Hey, Corser.
你好吗  哥们
What's up, man?
一般吧  你呢
Not much. You?
我把奶酪生产执照给烧了
Well, I burned my cheese license.
我听说了
I heard about that.
有什么负面影响吗
Was there any fallout?
一点都没有
Not a peep.
食品药监局已经知道了
I know the FDA Knows, by now...
但我还没收到任何通知
but I haven't heard a word.
你觉得接下来会怎样
So what do you think will happen?
不知道
No idea.
靠
Shit.
我能不能
Uh, could--
你好
Hello?
是我
It's me.
怎么了
What's up?
你有联系迪娜吗
Have you talked to Dena?
没有
No.
我以为我们现在不应该联系
No, I thought we weren't talking right now.
是啊  我也以为是这样
Yeah, well that's what I thought too,
可是她一直给我打电话
but she's been calling me a lot.
她为什么打给你
Why is she calling you?
不知道  但她确实找我了
I don't know, but she is.
她听起来不太好
And she doesn't seem like she's doing so good.
好吧  但我们不应该互相联络
Okay, but no one should be talking.
我们现在都不应该通电话
We-- we shouldn't even be talking right now.
我知道
Yep, I know,
但我们已经在通电话了
but it's happening.
你说她不太好是什么意思
So what do you mean, she's not doing so good?
你看新闻了吗
You read the news?
看了
Yeah.
她很难过
She's upset.
好吧  我也是
Yeah, well, me too.
他会出现的
He'll turn up.
你等着吧
You watch.
你觉得她应该不会
Well, you don't think she would,
做什么蠢事吧  会吗
like, do anything stupid, do you?
我不知道  所以我才打给你
I don't know. That's why I'm calling you.
好吧  这样
Okay, so...
也许我应该和她谈谈
so maybe I should go talk to her.
-也许吧  -好
- Yeah, maybe. - Yeah.
怎么了  你觉得我不应该这么做
What, you don't think I should?
我不知道  我不知道你们俩关系如何
I don't know. I don't know how it is between you two.
如果你觉得有用  那就打给她
If you think it would help, you should definitely talk to her.
如果没用  我也不知道了
If not, I don't know.
我就是想告诉你一声
I just wanted you to know.
就这样
That's all.
她好像不太好
She isn't doing that great.
好吧
Okay.
那你呢  你怎么样
So how-- how about you, though?
你还好吗
Are you-- are you okay?
我很好
I'm okay.
肯定的
Sure.
晚安
Good night.
我以为我们要分开一段时间
I thought we were gonna stay away for a while.
我只是想来看看你
Yeah, I just wanted to check in.
上车吧
Come on in.
哈蒙给你打电话了  对吧
Harmon called you, didn't he?
对  我们谈了一下
Yeah. We talked for a second.
他说你很不安
He said that you were worried.
就这样
That's all.
不安
Worried.
你想谈谈吗
Do you want to talk about it?
你要我说什么
What am I supposed to say?
你看过那个网站吗
Have you seen the website?
什么网站
What website?
你当然没看过
Of course you haven't seen it.
你关心这个干嘛
Why would you care?
我不知道你说的是哪个网站
I don't know what website you're talking about.
为了失踪露营者的那个
The one for the missing camper.
你应该看看
You should see it.
他的妻子  孩子  妈妈以及朋友们
All of his friends are posting,
都在找他
his wife, his kids, his mother.
真是难以置信
I can't believe this.
听好
Okay, look.
谁都不想发生这事
It's not what anyone wanted,
也许那个人没事
but the guy is probably fine.
我们什么也不知道
We don't know anything.
你说过  没人会受伤的
You said no one would get hurt.
他们却成了受害者
But they did.
我们还不知道  但是
We don't know that, but...
但是你感到不安是正常的
but it's natural for you to feel so upset.
这一点都不正常
There's nothing natural about this.
我们可以在冬天的时候行动
We could have done this in the winter
那时候没人在那里
when no one would be there.
你以为会发生什么
What did you think was gonna happen?
所以
So...
你打算怎么办
so what are you gonna do?
什么意思
What do you mean?
我的意思是  你有什么打算吗
I mean, are you going to do anything?
或者你能挺过去
Or are you going to be able to get through this
继续生活吗
and keep on going?
这是你来这里的原因吗
Is that why you're here?
你是怕我报警吗
Do you mean, am I gonna call the cops?
是怕我去拜访哈尔特一家
Am I gonna go visit the Halter family
告诉他们真相吗
and tell them what really happened?
我不知道  别烦我
I don't really know, so just leave me alone.
迪娜
Hey, Dena.
放开我
Let me go.
你弄疼我了
You're hurting me.
对不起
Sorry.
一定是三文鱼干的
I bet the salmon did it.
自杀式三文鱼
Like, suicide salmon,
组织起来
they, like, organized,
从鲟鱼或其它鱼那弄来了武器
got arms from the sturgeon or something, you know?
你听说过延龄湖里的朝鲜蓟吗
Did you hear about those artichokes at Trillium?
它们非常美味  好吃极了
They're so good, man. They're amazing.
上周有试吃
They had some on samples for last week.
我听说了
Yeah, yeah, I heard about that.
我听说比去年的好
I heard they were better than last year's.
那是一定的
That's for sure.
我们十点才开门
We don't open until 10:00.
给我五分钟就好
I'll be.. I'll be five minutes... less.
如果我为你破例
If I make an exception for you...
我听不到你说什么
I can't hear you.
我就得为所有人破例
I have to make an exception for everyone.
给我两分钟就好  可以吗
Okay, I'll be two minutes, okay?
就两分钟
I'll be two minutes.
在格林彼得大坝附近发现失踪露营者尸体
删除浏览记录
再见
Bye.
回见  兄弟
Later, man.
你又跟迪娜谈过了吗
You talk to Dena again?
现在是怎样
And what's happening?
她快崩溃了
She's taking it hard.
我也差不多
Yeah, well, join the club.
她跟你可不一样
Yeah, well, there's hard, and there's hard.
所以
So...
她会告诉别人吗
is she talking?
时间问题
It's just a matter of time.
一个人
One person.
就牺牲一个人
Okay? That's all it takes.
所以呢
So?
我不知道
I don't know.
这件事得解决
Something's got to happen.
你有办法吗
Oh, you got ideas?
没有  不过我不想进监狱
Nope, but jail don't sound too good to me.
我还想活久点
The time for this try life plus 300 years.
该死
Shit.
你好  乔希
Hi, Josh.
你好  最近怎样
Hey. How's it going?
很好
Good.
你好  乔希
Hey, Josh.
走吧
Okay, let's go.
走吧  小东西
Come on, guys. Come on.
-快走  -快
- Hey, come on. - Come on.
-斯科特  快走  -斯科特
- Scout, let's go. - Scout.
斯科特  快走
Scout, let's go.
-跟上  -斯科特
- Hey. - Scout.
过来
Here.
乔希  我能和你谈谈吗
Hey, Josh, can I talk to you for a second?
现在吗
Now?
就是现在
Yeah, now would be good.
怎么了
What's up?
我也不知道发生什么事
Now, I don't know exactly what's going on.
你干什么是你自己的事
What you do is your own business,
但人们已经开始谈论了
but people are talking.
你知道吗
You know that?
谁在谈论
Who's talking?
直接告诉我
You know, just tell me.
谁在谈论
Tell me who's talking.
迪娜和安昨晚谈过了
Dena and Anne talked last night.
她说什么了
And what did she say?
我不知道
I don't know.
她什么也不用说
She didn't have to say anything.
安太了解她了
Anne knows her too well.
安又不傻
Anne's not stupid.
迪娜还和谁说了
And who else is Dena talking to?
这不是重点
That's not the point.
我什么也不知道  可以吧
Now, I don't know anything, all right?
可以
All right.
我不知道发生了什么
I don't know what happened.
我也不需要知道
I don't ever have to know,
我更不想成为同谋
but I can't be an accomplice to this.
你不是  你什么也不知道
You're not. You don't even know anything.
你还是不懂  乔希  我们生活在这里
You're not getting it, Josh. We live here.
意味着我和我的家人都会受到牵连
That means I'm abetting. My whole family's abetting you.
你还不明白吗  我们可能会失去一切
Don't you get it, man? We could lose everything.
这事不会无缘无故平息
This is not gonna blow over, man.
做你该做的  把事情搞定
Do your thing, whatever you have to do,
千万别把我们拖下水
but don't take us down, all right?
你知道我们努力了多久才有这番景象吗
You know how long it took for us to make this?
乔希
Hey, Josh.
Josh.
怎么了
What's going on?
我听说你要离开这里
I hear you're taking off.
是的  至少离开一阵子
Oh, yeah, yeah, for a little while, at least.
现在吗
Right away?
你要
Are you...
你要去波特兰吗
are you gonna go up to Portland?
我想我可能很快也会去那里
'Cause I think I'm gonna be going up there soon actually.
不
Oh, no.
我往东部去  所以
I'm heading east, so...
-太可惜了  -抱歉
- Oh, bummer. - Sorry.
无论如何  是时候出去走走了
Well, it's a good time to be getting out, anyways.
为什么  你什么意思
Why? What do you mean?
你听说柯尔瑟的事了吗
Did you hear about Corser?
听说了
Well, yeah.
警察上门把他的电脑都收走了
The Feds knocked on his door and took away his computers.
为什么
Why?
说是因为他烧了生产执照
Burning the license, they said.
柯尔瑟说那都是胡扯
But Corser says that's bullshit,
一定另有原因
that they're on to something.
真是想太多了  对吧
It's out of this world, right?
那他怎么办
So what did he do?
他把电脑给他们了
He gave them the computers.
那些可不是食品检测员
You know, this is not the food inspectors, man.
他不敢惹他们
He's not gonna mess with these guys.
惊喜  走了
Surprise, come on.
好的
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
我一会就过去
I'll meet up with you in a second.
就像远走高飞  对吧
God, it's like, "Go away," Right?
你最近跟迪娜联系过吗
So have you talked to Dena lately?
没有
No. No.
我也没有
Yeah, me neither.
-好久没见到她了  -是啊
- I haven't seen her in a while. - Yeah.
听说她好像有点情绪低落之类的
I heard she was kind of down or something.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
莎拉说的
Yeah. That's what Sarah said.
我以为你知道些什么
I just... I thought you would know something.
我不知道
I don't.
那好吧
Okay, well...
如果你联系到她的话
if you talk to her,
让她给我电话  好吗
tell her to give me a call, okay?
可以
Okay.
晚安
Good night.
那真是太好了  谢谢你
That was amazing. Thank you.
希望这没有麻烦到你
Hope you don't get in trouble for this.
不会  奥黛丽很听话
No, Audrey's cool.
这让我释放了不少
This play just takes it out of me.
感觉好多了
I feel much better.
真是太好了
Good. I'm glad.
你得照顾好自己
You should really treat yourself too.
只是荨麻疹之类的
Oh, it's just hives or a rash or something,
我一有压力就会这样
whenever I'm stressed.
好好照顾自己
Well, try to take care of yourself.
如果这个周末有什么事  就给我电话
If anything happens this weekend, give me a call.
再见
See you.
吓死人了  乔希
What the fuck, Josh?
你在这里干嘛
What are you doing here?
出去  乔希  回家去
Get out, Josh. Go home.
我只是想看看你还好不
I just wanted to make sure that you're okay.
因为我
Because I've been,
个人感觉
personally,
不太好
not so good.
如果我感觉不太好
And if I'm not good,
你也感觉不太好的话
and you're not good, then...
-不  我很好  -不不不  我只是
- No, I'm fine. - No, no, no, I just...
我觉得我们要了解自己的感受
I just think it's important that we know what we feel.
我知道  我懂
Yeah, yeah, I get it. I got it.
很好  那就别打电话
Good, okay, now stay off the fucking phone.
别上网
Stay off the goddamn computer.
给我闭嘴
Don't open your mouth at all.
出去走走
Go somewhere else.
有必要的话就离开这里
Get out of town if you have to.
昨晚我去见她了
Yes, I went to see her last night.
那里像是
And, yeah, there was kind of like...
像是出了场意外
like an accident, and...
你在说迪吗
Are you talking about D?
你是说迪不会再碍事了吗
You're telling me D isn't in the picture anymore?
就这样了吗  她真的出局了吗
Is that it? She... Did she quit on this?
是的  她出局了
Yeah, she quit.
什么也别告诉我  我不想知道
Don't tell me anything. I don't want to know.
那只是个意外  我的意思是
Yeah, but, I mean, it was an accident, though. I mean, she...
我知道  你冷静点
I know. I know man. Just calm down. I know.
因为意外  她出局了
She quit by accident. Okay.
我也不知道
I don't know.
我在想  也许
Like, I was thinking, maybe, like,
我们可以去个什么地方
you and I could go somewhere,
安静点的
like, kind of quiet,
去一个完全陌生的地方
like just out in the middle of nowhere or something.
我东西很多
I got a lot of stuff.
我可以去接你
And I could come and get you.
我不知道你在哪  但我可以去接你
I can come and get you now. I don't know where you are.
你得赶紧逃了
You got to get real lost now.
赶紧逃  别回来
You got to get real lost and stay lost.
好的
Okay.
就这样了
That's it.
我知道
Yeah, I know.
有什么需要帮助的吗
You need any help?
没事  我看看就好
No. No, I'm good.
好的
Okay.
实际上
No, actually...
实际上我是来应聘的
Actually I'm here about that job.
好的
Oh, okay, cool.
蒂姆
Hey, Tim!
这人是来应聘的
This guy's here about the job.
太好了
Oh, great.
-你好  -你好
- Hi, there. - Hey.
你跟我到前台去吧
Why don't you come to the front desk with me.
填张申请表  好吗
We'll have you fill an application, okay?
好的
Okay.
你有销售经验吗
Do you have any retail experience?
很好
Great, great.
你住在附近吗
You from around here?
你有车吗
And do you have a car?
很好
Great.
给你
Well, here you go.
填下这个
If you want to just fill that out
填好了告诉我
and tell me when you're done,
我会把我需要填的填上
I'll fill in the parts I need to fill out,
然后就可以了  好吗
and we'll just take it from there, okay?
-好的  -很好
- Okay. - Great.